<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Quotes on Edward Manning</title>
    <link>http://edwardmanning.com/categories/quotes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Quotes on Edward Manning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 12:17:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://edwardmanning.com/categories/quotes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Quotes To Make You Think</title>
      <link>http://edwardmanning.com/2010/09/18/quotes-to-make-you-think/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2010 12:17:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edwardmanning.com/2010/09/18/quotes-to-make-you-think/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Far better it is to dare mighty things, to win glorious triumphs, even  though checkered by failure, than to take rank with those poor souls who  neither enjoy much nor suffer much, because they live in the gray  twilight that knows neither victory nor defeat.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Theodore Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;It is not the critic who counts, not the man who points  out how the strong man stumbled, or where the doer of deeds could have  done them better.  The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the  arena; whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood; who strives  valiantly; who errs and comes short again and again; who knows the great  enthusiasms, the great devotions, and spends himself in a worthy cause;  who, at best, knows in the end the triumph of high achievement; and  who, at the worst, if he fails, at least fails while daring greatly, so  that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who know  neither victory nor defeat.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;Theodore Roosevelt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Finish each day and be done with it. You have done what you could; some  blunders and absurdities have crept in; forget them as soon as you can.  Tomorrow is a new day; you shall begin it serenely and with too high a  spirit to be encumbered with your oldnonsense.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Ralph Waldo Emerson&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;You don&amp;rsquo;t have to change that much for it to make a great deal of  difference. A few simple disciplines can have a major impact on how your  life works out in the next 90 days, let alone in the next 12 months or  the next 3 years.&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash; Jim Rohn&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&amp;ldquo;Earn as much money as you possibly can and as quickly as you can. The  sooner you get money out of the way, the sooner you will be able to get  to the rest of your problems in style.&amp;rdquo;&amp;ndash; Jim Rohn&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>