<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Self Help on Edward Manning</title>
    <link>http://edwardmanning.com/tags/self-help/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Self Help on Edward Manning</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 19:51:58 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://edwardmanning.com/tags/self-help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Thou didst thy best. That is success.</title>
      <link>http://edwardmanning.com/2009/03/30/thou-didst-thy-best-that-is-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2009 19:51:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://edwardmanning.com/2009/03/30/thou-didst-thy-best-that-is-success/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I was watching &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ted.com/index.php/talks/john_wooden_on_the_difference_between_winning_and_success.html&#34;&gt;John Wooden&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.ted.com/&#34;&gt;Ted Talks&lt;/a&gt; when he made the following quote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;At God&#39;s footstool, to confess,
A poor soul knelt and bowed his head.
&#34;I failed,&#34; he cried. The master said,
&#34;Thou didst thy best. That is success.&#34;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I have to say, I was rather moved.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;&#34;Thou didst thy best. That is success.&#34;&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All too often, we look around and compare ourselves against what we see. We rate our achievements against those of other people, when the true test of accomplishment is against &lt;strong&gt;our&lt;/strong&gt; personal best, not someone else’s.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the past, I have not done my best. Worse - I have not even &lt;em&gt;tried&lt;/em&gt; to do my best. I have coasted along, doing just enough to get by. Just enough to pay the bills. Just enough to get through school. I feel I have wasted those years. I have whittled away at time, till all that was left is the shavings of my life scattered on the floor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It changes. Now. Today. Right this second.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter how poor at something I turn out to be, I want to be able to look at my progress and say &lt;em&gt;&amp;ldquo;I did my best. That is success.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/em&gt; That is the promise to myself.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;See you on the far side of better.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>